翻译/压制/字幕制作：HAF半个水果
翻译支持：Deepl 翻译
Hello everyone so i set up a little fake computer here
大家好，我在这里建立了一个小的假电脑
英语字幕由 Youtube 自动生成，字幕仅供参考,欢迎在弹幕中指正！
That looks kinda real if you think about it
如果你仔细看看，这看起来还挺真实的
It's also kind of slow it's 30 fps it's running minecraft at 30 fps in window mode
它也有点慢，30帧，在窗口模式下以30帧运行Minecraft
But
但
It's just gonna make it better because we are going to scan bait
这只会让它变得更好，因为我们要去扫描诱饵
In the previous video the number on the side did not work or well it worked but it redirected me at another scammer that
在之前的视频中，边上的号码没有工作，或者它工作了，但它把我转到了另一个骗子那里
Told me something about hundred dollar rebate cards i really care about it
告诉我关于百元回扣卡的事情，我真的很关心
So in this video we are going to try again
所以在这段视频中，我们将再次尝试
And i'm pretty sure this number definitely works i just have to wait a little bit because they only start working at like 10 a.m mountain time
我很确定这个号码肯定能用，只是要等一下，因为他们只在山区时间上午10点开始工作
Mountain time is nine hours behind moscow time
山区时间比莫斯科时间晚九个小时
And it's almost seven
而现在已经快到七点了
And in the meantime i set this
在此期间，我设置了这个
Little
小小的
Vm up
Just i guess to make it look a little bit legit to the scammer although you can see vmware here vmware tools
这是为了让骗子看起来有点合法，虽然你可以在这里看到vmware工具
I just want to see the initial reaction of the scammer to the fact that it is a vm and i was trolling him
我只是想看看骗子的最初反应，这是一个虚拟机，我在嘲弄他
Allready so
就这样了
Yeah that'd be looking pretty good
这看起来很不错
I'm gonna copy this over and know why i used to do that as a kid
我要把这个复制过来，知道为什么我小时候会这么做了吧
Unless you know that i was i'm a gullible person and i'm gonna do whatever
除非你知道我是一个容易受骗的人，而我要做的事情就是编一个故事
This story is basically that i was playing the blog game i decided to download Bandicam
这个故事基本上是，我在玩博客游戏时，想要下载Bandicam
I got i got some scummy ad and it redirected me at their website
点到了一些虚假的广告，并将我转到了他们的网站上
And the by time it's already seven so i guess let's call them up
而现在已经是7点了，所以让我们给他打电话吧
Thank you for calling support my name is evelyn how may i help you
谢谢你呼叫支持，我的名字是伊夫林，我可以帮你吗
Hello evelyn is this microsoft tech support
你好，伊夫林，这是微软的技术支持吗
Yeah this is microsoft tech support help me help you today
是的，这是微软的技术支持，今天由我帮助你
I got a website that told me that uh my computer got a virus and there was your toll-free number i don't know what to do it's like full screen doesn't let me go anywhere
我进到一个网站，告诉我，我的电脑中了病毒，有你的免费电话号码，
我不知道该怎么做，好像全屏了，不让我离开
Sure
好的
So uh what kind of issue are you facing with the computer
那么，你的电脑有什么样的问题呢
uh there is a website that went full screen and it tells me that my computer is infected
有一个网站全屏了，它告诉我，我的电脑被感染了
And i have to contact tech support
我不得不联系技术支持
Okay
好的
All right so so and what were you doing on the computer when you received the message
那么，当你收到信息时，你在电脑上做什么
I was trying to download Bandicam uh from some Specials site and it redirected me to another website and now here we are
我想从一些特别的网站上下载Bandicam ，但它把我转到了另一个网站，就变成这样了
Okay
好的
All right so in order for me to help you i need to first connect to your computer to run some scan and to find out what the cause of the problem is
为了帮助你，我需要首先连接到你的电脑，进行一些扫描，找出问题的原因
So uh if it's if it's okay for you or if you're at the computer then i can quickly connect to the computer so we can check out the issue
所以，如果...如果你可以的话，或者你在电脑前的话，
我可以快速连接到电脑上，这样我们就可以检查出这个问题
Yeah that sounds good
很不错（即答）
Okay all right so are you in front of the computer
好的，那现在你在电脑前吗
Yeah
是的
Okay all right do one thing can you hold down the windows key on the keyboard and the letter R at the same time
好的，做一件事，你能不能同时按住键盘上的windows键和字母 R
Yeah
好
Hold up
按住了
I did
完成
All right and uh do you see a small run box on the left uh on the left corner if you type the name of the program folder document
好的，你是否看到一个小的运行框在左边，在左边的角落，要求你输入程序文件夹文件的名称
Yeah i do
看到了
Okay what do you see on your screen
好的，你在屏幕上看到什么
Uh i'm currently seeing a run box on the top left of my screen
我目前在屏幕的左上方看到一个运行框
okay so type in there uh www dot
好，输入3W.
Dot
点
18 000
Yes?
完成？
Okay i did
完成了
Okay
Now uh you can click on uhokay or either
现在呃，你可以点击OK或者是
I already did i already did i'm on the website it's either fast support or click here to join sessions
我已经做了，我在网站上，要么是快速支持，要么是点击这里加入会议
继续点击加入会议
正在下载
继续.....好吧，还在下载中，下载完成后告诉我
How it's qs.exe
怎么做，它是 qs.exe
Yes click on open
好的，打开它
Okay
Uh all right i clicked run
好了，我运行了
Open the file?
打开了文件？
Okay once you open the file then what do you see
好的，打开文件后看到什么
I see your id and password
我看到你的ID和密码
Okay uh please share the id and password
好的，分享你的ID和密码
Yeah sure
好的（即答）
Six zero zero
6 0 0
eight seven nine
8 7 9
Okay
Five seven seven
5 7 7
all right the password
好的，密码
five five
5 5
ucd
Seven
Ok allow me a moment of me to connect to your computer
好的，请允许我稍等片刻，我将连接到你的电脑上
Take her then
等下联系你
Thank you
谢谢你
And so where is the window security warning
那么，有没有Windows的安全警告呢？
There it is
有
Okay
I heard a floppy drive click
我听到软盘驱动器的咔哒声
She hung up for some reason
不知道什么原因她挂断了电话
She's continuing to do something on my computer
她继续在我的电脑上做一些事情
She deleted all my desktop icons
她删了我所有桌面图标
What's up with that
怎么回事
No my minecraft world
不，我的世界
She's gonna syskey my computer let's go
她要加密我的电脑，开始吧
So was that it
所以就这样
Here are my icons
这有我的图标
Restore them
恢复他们
What happened though
发生了一些事
What's syskey
syskey是什么
I still want explanations
我还想要再探险一下
let's call her up again
再打一次电话给她
Hello
Hello kevin i'm doing good thank you for asking
你好，凯文，谢谢你的询问，问题是
The problem is i already called your tech support
i got a website that told i was infected with
我已经打电话给你们的技术支持，我进到一个网站，告诉我被感染了
Ransomware or whatever some kind of virus
勒索病毒或其他某种病毒
And i called this number before and i got greeted by evelyn she helped me
我之前打过这个电话，伊夫林接待了我，她帮助了我
I guess she removed my desktop icons and turned on syskey and i'm currently i currently reboot it
我猜她删除了我的桌面图标，并打开了syskey，我目前正在重启
I don't know what to do am is my computer still infected
我不知道该怎么做，我的电脑还在被感染
What should i do
我要怎么做
Well i told you before i opened the one one of the websites told me that my computer is infected with malware
我之前告诉过你，我打开了一个网站，其中一个网站告诉我，我的电脑被感染了恶意软件
And i called this number and then uh there was a girl called evelyn and she helped me
我打了这个电话，然后有一个叫伊夫林的女孩，她帮了我
She removed mydesktop icons and turned on syskey and my computer has rebooted
她删了我的桌面图标，并打开了syskey，我的电脑已经重启了
So is my computer free of infection she didn't call me back or this is anything
那么，我的电脑是否感染，她没有给我回电话，或者意味着什么
What
Uh it's good to go you can use the computer
可以了，你可以使用电脑了
*Imfao 是作者写的，不知何意*
Oh so i don't have to care about anything anymore right everything the infection is clean
所以我不必再担心了，所有的病毒都已清除
Okay
All right thank you
好的，感谢你
Thank you goodbye
谢谢，再见
I guess they understood it was a vm or something
我猜他们知道这是一个虚拟机或什么东西
Or
或者
The language barrier
语言不通
One of these two
是其中之一吧
我打了三次电话，他们把我拉黑了
原视频上传时间：2022年8月14日   原作者：Enderman
原标题：Calling the -Microsoft Tech Support-
在 Youtube 上关注作者
翻译/压制/字幕制作：HAF半个水果
翻译支持：Deepl 翻译
字幕制作不易，喜欢的话支持一下我吧